Edward Dorn Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
Boulder Monthly. Dorn, Edward. “Acid Rain in the Mountains.” Boulder, Colorado: Boulder Monthly Magazine, Inc., 1979. Volume I, Number X, August 1979. Dodd Call No.
Boulder Monthly. Dorn, Edward. “Fear and Clothing at the Blue Note.” Boulder, Colorado: Boulder Monthly Magazine, Inc., 1979. Volume I, Number XII, October 1979. Dodd Call No.
Boulder Monthly. Dorn, Edward. “H2O: A Review of Many Waters.” Boulder, Colorado: Boulder Monthly Magazine, Inc., 1979. Volume I, Number VIII, June 1979. Dodd Call No.
Markings 1. Dresman, Paul. “Summer Stars.” La Jolla: Roadwork, 1979. Inscribed by P. D. Focus. August 28, 1983. Dodd Call No.
Golding, Alan. “History, Mutation, and the Mutation of History in Edward Dorn's Slinger.” Dodd Call No.
Sagetrieb, Rakosi, Carl, ed. Orono: University of Maine at Orono, 1987. Volume 6, Number 1, Spring 1987. Inscribed by A. G. Dodd Call No.
Hombre Y Jaguar Revista de Literatura. Number 7. Dodd Call No.
Impact. Volume 10, Number 44, August 18, 1987. Dodd Call No.
Tens. Little, Bill, ed. Number 4, December 1972. Dodd Call No.
Grosseteste Review, Longville, Tim, ed. Volume 10, Numbers1-4, Summer 1977. Annotated by E. D. Dodd Call No.
Grosseteste Review, Longville, Tim, ed. Volume 12, 1979. Dodd Call No.
Grosseteste Review, Longville, Tim, ed. Volume 13, 1980/81. Inscribed. Dodd Call No.
Grosseteste Review, Longville, Tim, ed. Volume 15, 1983-84. Dodd Call No.
The News. Lopez, Tony, ed.Dodd Call No. Number 1, April 1987. Dodd Call No.
Cottonwood Review. Low, Denise and Robin Tawney, eds.Dod Call No. Number 22. Spring 1980. Dodd Call No.
Morrow Books for Winter 1966-1967. New York City: William Morrow and Company, Inc. Dodd Call No.
Muse. Issue 13, Oct/Nov 1981. Dodd Call No.
The New Republic. Volume 174, Number 17, Issue 3198, April 24, 1976. Dodd Call No.
New York Rocker. New York City: Over The Hill Productions Inc., 1978. Volume I, Number 13, July-August 1978. Dodd Call No.
On The Road. Boulder: Naropa Institute, 1982. Dodd Call No.
Other World Poetry. Volume 1, Number 1, July 1979. Inscribed. Dodd Call No.
Peace News. Number 1548, February 25, 1966. Dodd Call No.
Pendragon. Volume 2, Number 1, Spring 1983. Dodd Call No.
Infolio. Raworth, Tom, ed. March 1986, 1 Jul 1986 - 20 Nov 1987 (1-100), 1 Oct 1990 - 12 Jun 1991 (12). Dodd Call No.
Perfect Bound. Robinson, Peter and Bill Bennett, eds. Cambridge: Bluebell Printing Company King St., 1976. Annotated by E.D. #460 of 700. Dodd Call No.
Time. December 13, 1976. Dodd Call No.
Toothpick, Lisbon & the Orcas Islands. Wiater, Michael. “Alive and Well.” Volume 2, Number 3, Issue 4. Dodd Call No.
Bibliography
About the Author:
Ackroyd, Peter.. “In Public,” Spectator, 10 January 1975 pp. 17-18.
Duberman, Martin. Black Mountain An Exploration in Community.New York: Dutton, 1972.
Lockwood, William J. “Ed Dorn's Mystique of the Real: His Poems for North America,” Contemporary Literature, 19 (Winter 1978): 59-79.
Perloff, Marjorie. Review of The Collected Poems and Slinger. New Republic, 174 (24 April 1976): 22-26.
Streeter, David. A Bibliography of Ed Dorn. New York: Phoenix Bookshop, ">1973.
Westling, Donald. “A Bibliography on Edward Dorn for America,” Parnassus: Poetry in Review, 5 (Spring-Summer 1977): 142-160.
Zavatsky, Bill. Review of The Collected Poems. New York Times Book Review, 17 October 1976, pp. 32-34
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Subjects:
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Personal Papers.; Manuscripts.; Notebooks.; Publications.; Photographs.
Occupations:
Poet.; Author.; Educator.
Restrictions on Access
Several items have been restricted. Contact the curator for further information.
Acquisition Information
The collection was purchased by the University in several installments.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Correspondence to Edward Dorn, undated, 1956-1993
  - Subseries A: Major Correspondence, undated, 1956-1993
    - Abrams, Sam, 1973-1993 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
    - Adams, Mariana, 1980-1983 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
    - Alexander, Charles, 1979-1990 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
    - Allen, Donald, 1965-1991 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
    - Alpert, Barry, 1971-1977 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
    - Am Here Books, undated (Box 1:, Folder 6)
    - The Alternative Press (see: Mikolowski, Ken)
    - American Poetry (see: Bartlett, Lee)
    - Ardinger, Rick, 1988-1989 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
    - Arnica Press (see: Watson, William)
    - AWP, Associated Writing Programs (see: Rector, Liam)
    - B C Research, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
    - Back, Steven Oskar?, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
    - Baillis, Bruce, 1964-1965 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
    - Baraka, Amiri, 1981 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
    - Bartlett, Lee, 1985-1988 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
    - Baskin, Suzzanne, 1984-1986 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
    - Behymer, Philip, 1983 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
    - Beltrametti, Franco, 1979-1992 (Box 1:, Folder 15)
    - Benson, Joyce, 1975-1991 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
    - Benton, William, 1987-1988 (Box 1:, Folder 17)
    - Berlin, Andrew, 1977-1982 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
    - Berlin, Lucia, undated (Box 1:, Folder 19)
    - Berlin, Lucia, 1976-1977 (Box 1:, Folder 20)
    - Berlin, Lucia, 1978-1981 (Box 2:, Folder 21)
    - Berlin, Lucia, 1982-1984 (Box 2:, Folder 22)
    - Berlin, Lucia, 1985-1986 (Box 2:, Folder 23)
    - Berlin, Lucia, 1987-1989 (Box 2:, Folder 24)
    - Berlin, Lucia, 1990-1993 (Box 2:, Folder 25)
    - Bertholf, Robert, 1971-1989 (Box 2:, Folder 26)
    - Bertolino, Jim, 1980-1986 (Box 2:, Folder 27)
    - Bialy, Harvey, 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 28)
    - Binni, Francesco, 1980-1991 (Box 2:, Folder 29)
    - Black Mesa Press, 1983-1984 (Box 2:, Folder 30)
    - Black Sparrow Press (see also: Martin, John), 1972-1993 (Box 2:, Folder 31)
    - Blevins, Rich, 1980-1991 (Box 3:, Folder 32)
    - Bloody Twin Press (see: Richards, Brian)
    - Boise State University (see: Pavesic, Max)
    - Book People, undated (Box 3:, Folder 33)
    - Boston Herald (see: Kimball, George)
    - Bowling Green State University (see: McCord, Howard)
    - Boyle, Kaye, 1982 (Box 3:, Folder 34)
    - Brakhage, Jane, 1973-1988 (Box 3:, Folder 35)
    - Brakhage, Stan, 1964-1972 (Box 3:, Folder 36)
    - Brakhage, Stan, 1973-1990 (Box 3:, Folder 37)
    - Brigade, Kuksu, 1982-1983 (Box 3:, Folder 38)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1981-1987 (Box 3:, Folder 39)
    - Brotherston, Gordon, 1970-1991 (Box 3:, Folder 40)
    - Brown, Harvey, 1964-1985 (Box 3:, Folder 41)
    - Brutus, Dennis (see: Webster, Lee)
    - Buck, Fred, 1964-1982 (Box 3:, Folder 42)
    - Butterfield, Herb, 1974-1989 (Box 3:, Folder 43)
    - Butterick, George, 1975-1988 (Box 3:, Folder 44)
    - Caddel, Ric, 1975-1981 (Box 4:, Folder 45)
    - Callahan, Robert, 1973-1986 (Box 4:, Folder 46)
    - Cambridge, 1980 (Box 4:, Folder 47)
    - Cantrell, Emily, 1983-1990 (Box 4:, Folder 48)
    - Clark, Tom, undated (Box 4:, Folder 49)
    - Clark, Tom, 1965-1979 (Box 4:, Folder 50)
    - Clark, Tom, 1980 January - September (Box 4:, Folder 51)
    - Clark, Tom, 1980 October - December (Box 4:, Folder 52)
    - Clark, Tom, 1981 January - June (Box 4:, Folder 53)
    - Clark, Tom, 1981 July - December (Box 5:, Folder 54)
    - Clark, Tom, 1982 January - June (Box 5:, Folder 55)
    - Clark, Tom, 1982 July - December (Box 5:, Folder 56)
    - Clark, Tom, 1983 January - August (Box 5:, Folder 57)
    - Clark, Tom, 1983 September - December (Box 5:, Folder 58)
    - Clark, Tom, 1984 January - May (Box 5:, Folder 59)
    - Clark, Tom, 1984 June - December (Box 6:, Folder 60)
    - Clark, Tom, 1985 (Box 6:, Folder 61)
    - Clark, Tom, 1986 (Box 6:, Folder 62)
    - Clark, Tom, 1987 (Box 6:, Folder 63)
    - Clark, Tom, 1988 (Box 6:, Folder 64)
    - Clark, Tom, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 65)
    - Clark, Tom (***1 restricted letter***), 1990 (Box 6:, Folder 66)
    - Clark, Tom, 1991 (Box 7:, Folder 67)
    - Clark, Tom, 1992 (Box 7:, Folder 68)
    - Clark, Tom, 1993 (Box 7:, Folder 69)
    - Clarke, Jack, 1978-1991 (Box 7:, Folder 70)
    - Cochran, Jeff, 1985-1991 (Box 7:, Folder 71)
    - Collom, Jack, 1965-1984 (Box 7:, Folder 72)
    - Conjunctions (see: Morrow, Bradford)
    - Connett, Phyllis, 1983-1985 (Box 7:, Folder 73)
    - Contemporanei (see: Binni, Francesco)
    - Continental Drift (see: Sturgeon, Tandy)
    - Credences (see: Bertholf, Robert)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1955-1960 (Box 7:, Folder 74)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1961-1962 (Box 7:, Folder 75)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1963-1965 (Box 7:, Folder 76)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1966-1970 (Box 7:, Folder 77)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1974-1993 (Box 8:, Folder 78)
    - d'Or, Vic, 1973-1977 (Box 8:, Folder 79)
    - Dahl, David, 1981-1988 (Box 8:, Folder 80)
    - Dailey, Joel, 1983-1987 (Box 8:, Folder 81)
    - Daley, John, 1974-1977 (Box 8:, Folder 82)
    - Daley, John, 1978-1980 (Box 8:, Folder 83)
    - Daley, John, 1981-1984 (Box 8:, Folder 84)
    - Daley, John, 1985-1993 (Box 8:, Folder 85)
    - Davidson, Michael, 1972-1983 (Box 8:, Folder 86)
    - Davie, Donald, 1965-1987 (Box 8:, Folder 87)
    - Dawson, Fielding, 1963-1990 (Box 9:, Folder 88)
    - De Lapp, Robert, 1977-1979 (Box 9:, Folder 89)
    - DeMers, Tom, 1982-1984 (Box 9:, Folder 90)
    - Dickison, Swift, 1976-1983 (Box 9:, Folder 91)
    - Donovan, Brad, 1979-1985 (Box 9:, Folder 92)
    - Dorn, Edward, 1960-1990 (Box 9:, Folder 93)
    - Dorn, Jennifer, 1968-1989 (Box 9:, Folder 94)
    - Dorn, Kidd, 1978-1981 (Box 9:, Folder 95)
    - Dorn, Maya, 1981-1983 (Box 9:, Folder 96)
    - Dresman, Paul, 1976-1992 (Box 9:, Folder 97)
    - Duke University Press (see: Ferguson, Joanne)
    - Dunbar, John, 1976-1983 (Box 10:, Folder 98)
    - Dunbar, Margaret, 1981-1985 (Box 10:, Folder 99)
    - Dunbar, Robert, 1975-1987 (Box 10:, Folder 100)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1986 (Box 10:, Folder 101)
    - Echo-Hawk, Roger, 1983-1985 (Box 10:, Folder 102)
    - Economou, George, 1973-1992 (Box 10:, Folder 103)
    - Edith C. Blum Art Institute, 1985-1987 (Box 10:, Folder 104)
    - Eshleman, Clayton, 1970-1973 (Box 10:, Folder 105)
    - The Eternal Network (see: d'Or, Vic)
    - Fackler, Herb, 1977-1991 (Box 10:, Folder 106)
    - Ferguson, Joanne, 1983-1992 (Box 10:, Folder 107)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library (see: Rector, Liam)
    - Foster, Sesshu, 1984-1988 (Box 10:, Folder 108)
    - Four Seasons Foundation (see: Allen, Donald)
    - Fox, Willard “Skip”, 1982-1990 (Box 10:, Folder 109)
    - Foye, Raymond, 1985-1986 (Box 10:, Folder 110)
    - Gaffigan, Jacques, 1979-1985 (Box 11:, Folder 111)
    - Gauggel, Karl Hermann?, 1986-1989 (Box 11:, Folder 112)
    - Gery, John, 1979-1987 (Box 11:, Folder 113)
    - Gifford, Barry, 1985-1988 (Box 11:, Folder 114)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1979-1985 (Box 11:, Folder 115)
    - Glickfield, Cheryl, 1978 (Box 11:, Folder 116)
    - Goddard College (see: Grossinger, Richard)
    - Goldfarb, Sidney, 1978-1992 (Box 11:, Folder 117)
    - Golding, Alan, 1980-1990 (Box 11:, Folder 118)
    - Goodwin, Sister, 1977-1985 (Box 11:, Folder 119)
    - Grey Fox Press (see: Allen, Donald)
    - Gridley, Roy, 1968-1992 (Box 11:, Folder 120)
    - Grosseteste Press (see: Longville, Tim)
    - Grossinger, Richard, 1971-1973 (Box 11:, Folder 121)
    - Guillot, Linne, 1981-1987 (Box 11:, Folder 122)
    - Gustafson, Jim, 1984-1995 (Box 11:, Folder 123)
    - Hagedorn, Jessica, 1982-1988 (Box 12:, Folder 124)
    - Hall, David, 1965-1969 (Box 12:, Folder 125)
    - Handlet, Caroline, 1971-1985 (Box 12:, Folder 126)
    - Haut, Woody, 1984-1991 (Box 12:, Folder 127)
    - Herd, Dale, 1970-1978 (Box 12:, Folder 128)
    - Hernandez Cruz, Victor, 1979-1991 (Box 12:, Folder 129)
    - Hipparchia Press (see: Callahan, Robert)
    - Holbrook, 1974-1986 (Box 12:, Folder 130)
    - Hollo, Anselm, 1971-1982 (Box 12:, Folder 131)
    - Hoogstraten, Harry, 1979-1992 (Box 12:, Folder 132)
    - Hope, Andrew, 1976-1985 (Box 12:, Folder 133)
    - Howard, James, 1987-1989 (Box 12:, Folder 134)
    - Hyner, Stefan, 1987-1992 (Box 12:, Folder 135)
    - Idaho State University (see: Sturgeon, Tandy)
    - Indiana University (see: Alpert, Barry)
    - Innskeep, J. H., 1981-1986 (Box 13:, Folder 136)
    - Irby, Ken, 1965-1993 (Box 13:, Folder 137)
    - Jacobus, Terry, 1974-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 138)
    - Jacobus, Terry, 1984-1992 (Box 13:, Folder 139)
    - Jesus College (see: Wilkinson, John)
    - Johnson, Joyce, 1964-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 140)
    - Joris, Pierre, 1977-1980 (Box 13:, Folder 141)
    - Kahn, Greg, 1983-1986 (Box 13:, Folder 142)
    - Kahn, Paul, 1985-1986 (Box 13:, Folder 143)
    - Kano, Masako, 1980-1981 (Box 14:, Folder 144)
    - Keeble, John, 1979-1990 (Box 14:, Folder 145)
    - Keeler, Greg, 1984-1993 (Box 14:, Folder 146)
    - Kent State University (see: Bertholf, Robert)
    - Kerouac, Jack, 1959 (Box 14:, Folder 147)
    - Kimball, George, 1973-1989 (Box 14:, Folder 148)
    - Kitchell, Marilyn, 1984-1989 (Box 14:, Folder 149)
    - Köhler, Michael, 1974-1976 (Box 14:, Folder 150)
    - Kolokithas, Dawn, 1982-1986 (Box 14:, Folder 151)
    - Krapf, Norbert, 1984-1985 (Box 14:, Folder 152)
    - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated (Box 14:, Folder 153)
    - La Charity, Ralph, 1976-1988 (Box 14:, Folder 154)
    - Leacock, Richard, 1986-1990 (Box 14:, Folder 155)
    - Lesicka, Rex, 1976-1977 (Box 14:, Folder 156)
    - Levitt, Paul, 1978-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 157)
    - Levy, William, 1981-1988 (Box 15:, Folder 158)
    - Lewis, Robert, 1974-1987 (Box 15:, Folder 159)
    - Lipman, Joel, 1985-1988 (Box 15:, Folder 160)
    - Little, Bill, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 161)
    - Long Island University (see: Economou, George)
    - Long, Anton, 1977 (Box 15:, Folder 162)
    - Longville, Tim, 1981 (Box 15:, Folder 163)
    - Lopez, Tony, 1984-1988 (Box 15:, Folder 164)
    - Low, Denise, 1979-1985 (Box 15:, Folder 165)
    - Lytle, Nonna, 1978-1987 (Box 15:, Folder 166)
    - MacAdams, Lewis, 1972-1978 (Box 15:, Folder 167)
    - Mann, Ellen “El”, 1974-1985 (Box 15:, Folder 168)
    - Martin, John, 1967-1971 (Box 15:, Folder 169)
    - McClure, Michael, 1968-1978 (Box 15:, Folder 170)
    - McCord, Howard, 1985-1989 (Box 15:, Folder 171)
    - McCrary, Jim, 1976-1992 (Box 15:, Folder 172)
    - McNaughton, Duncan, 1973-1991 (Box 15:, Folder 173)
    - McPheron, William, 1983-1988 (Box 15:, Folder 174)
    - Meador, Pat, 1980-1991 (Box 16:, Folder 175)
    - Michelson, Peter, 1974-1992 (Box 16:, Folder 176)
    - Mikolowski, Ken, 1974-1991 (Box 16:, Folder 177)
    - Miller, Jeffrey, 1979-1980 (Box 16:, Folder 178)
    - Miller, Jeffrey, 1981-1990 (Box 16:, Folder 179)
    - Montana State University (see: Keeler, Greg)
    - Montgomery, Stuart, 1965 (Box 16:, Folder 180)
    - Morgan, Hedley, 1980-1985 (Box 16:, Folder 181)
    - Moritz, John, 1968-1992 (Box 16:, Folder 182)
    - Morris, James Ryan, n. d. (Box 16:, Folder 183)
    - Morrow, Bradford, 1979-1989 (Box 16:, Folder 184)
    - Myers, Michael, 1971-1972 (Box 16:, Folder 185)
    - Narapo Institute (see: Waldeman, Anne)
    - National Poetry Centre (see: Vas Dias, Robert)
    - Navero, Bud, 1976-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 186)
    - Nets (see: Little, Bill)
    - New College of California (see: Kolokithas, Dawn)
    - Nisbet, Jim, 1985-1986 (Box 16:, Folder 187)
    - North Carolina Wesleyan College (see: Smith, Leverett)
    - Notley, Alice, 1980-1987 (Box 16:, Folder 188)
    - O'Brien, John, 1980-1984 (Box 17:, Folder 189)
    - Obermayr, Raymond, 1974-1992 (Box 17:, Folder 190)
    - Okamura, Arthur, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 191)
    - Okamura, Simone [Ellis], 1980-1981 (Box 17:, Folder 192)
    - Okamura, Simone [Ellis], 1982-1987 (Box 17:, Folder 193)
    - Olson, Charles, 1956-1963 (Box 17:, Folder 194-227)
    - Olson, Charles, 1963-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 228-314)
    - One World Poetry, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 315)
    - Oppenheimer, Joel, 1966-1988 (Box 18:, Folder 316)
    - Opstedal, Kevin, 1986-1993 (Box 18:, Folder 317)
    - Pavesic, Max, 1976-1988 (Box 19:, Folder 318)
    - Peck, Daniel, 1986-1988 (Box 19:, Folder 319)
    - Permanent Press (see: Vas Dias, Robert)
    - Perry, Ginger, 1981 (Box 19:, Folder 320)
    - Pickard, Tom, 1974-1990 (Box 19:, Folder 321)
    - Piper, Paul, 1983-1988 (Box 19:, Folder 322)
    - The Poetry Center (see: MacAdams, Lewis)
    - Poetry News, 1980 (Box 19:, Folder 323)
    - Potts, Charles, 1974-1991 (Box 19:, Folder 324)
    - Powell, Donald, 1979-1981 (Box 19:, Folder 325)
    - Preston, Scott, 1963-1991 (Box 19:, Folder 326)
    - Providence Publishing Corporation (see: Lewis, Robert)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, undated (Box 19:, Folder 327)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1961-1962 (Box 19:, Folder 328)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1963 (Box 19:, Folder 329)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1964 (Box 19:, Folder 330)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1965 (Box 19:, Folder 331)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1966 (Box 19:, Folder 332)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1969-1970 (Box 19:, Folder 333)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1971-1974 (Box 20:, Folder 334)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1975-1976 (Box 20:, Folder 335)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1977-1978 (Box 20:, Folder 336)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1979-1980 (Box 20:, Folder 337)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1981-1983 (Box 20:, Folder 338)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1984-1987 (Box 20:, Folder 339)
    - Prynne, Jeremy, 1988-1992 (Box 20:, Folder 340)
    - Quagliano, Tony, 1987-1989 (Box 20:, Folder 341)
    - Randall, Margaret, 1965-1969 (Box 20:, Folder 342)
    - Raworth, Tom, undated (Box 21:, Folder 343)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1963-1973 (Box 21:, Folder 344)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1974-1976 (Box 21:, Folder 345)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1977 (Box 21:, Folder 346)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1978-1979 (Box 21:, Folder 347)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1980 (Box 21:, Folder 348)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1981 (Box 21:, Folder 349)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1982 (Box 21:, Folder 350)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1983 (Box 22:, Folder 351)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1984 (Box 22:, Folder 352)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1985 (Box 22:, Folder 353)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1986 (Box 22:, Folder 354)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1987 (Box 22:, Folder 355)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1988 (Box 22:, Folder 356)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1989-1992 (Box 22:, Folder 357)
    - Rector, Liam [Ron], 1987 (Box 22:, Folder 358)
    - Redford, James, 1992 (Box 22:, Folder 359)
    - The Regulator (see: McCord, Howard)
    - The Review of Contemporary Fiction (see: O'Brien, John)
    - Richards, Brian, 1988 (Box 22:, Folder 360)
    - Rochester Institute of Technology (see: Abrams, Sam)
    - Robinson, Peter, 1976 (Box 22:, Folder 361)
    - Rodney, Janet, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 362)
    - Rolling Stock (see: Michelson, Peter, Dorn, Edward)
    - Rose, Bob, 1973-1976 (Box 22:, Folder 363)
    - S Press (see: Köhler, Michael)
    - Safdie, Joe, 1979-1992 (Box 23:, Folder 364)
    - Salt-Works Press (see: Kitchell, Marilyn)
    - Samaan, Ruth, 1987-1988 (Box 23:, Folder 365)
    - Sanders, Ed, 1980-1990 (Box 23:, Folder 366)
    - Schneider, Byron, 1983-1984 (Box 23:, Folder 367)
    - Schuchat, Simon, 1972-1979 (Box 23:, Folder 368)
    - Sedgwick, Nicholas, 1979-1981 (Box 23:, Folder 369)
    - Sedgwick, Nicholas, 1982-1992 (Box 23:, Folder 370)
    - Sheldon Jackson College (see: Goodwin, Sister)
    - Shevelow, Kathryn, 1975-1977 (Box 23:, Folder 371)
    - Simmons, Al, 1975-1987 (Box 23:, Folder 372)
    - Skratz, G. P., 1976-1992 (Box 23:, Folder 373)
    - Smith, Harry, 1980 (Box 23:, Folder 374)
    - Smith, Leverett “Terry”, 1980-1987 (Box 23:, Folder 375)
    - SOMOS (Society of the Muse of the Southwest), 1985-1990 (Box 24:, Folder 376)
    - Sotomayor, Preman, 1986-1991 (Box 24:, Folder 377)
    - Southern, David, 1973-1983 (Box 24:, Folder 378)
    - Southern, David, 1984-1992 (Box 24:, Folder 379)
    - Southern, Susan, 1973 (Box 24:, Folder 380)
    - Sparrow, undated (Box 24:, Folder 381)
    - Stanford University Libraries (see: McPheron, William)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo, 1984-1985 (Box 24:, Folder 382)
      (see also: Bertholf, Robert, McPheron, William)
    - State University of New York College at Oneonta (see: Meador, Pat)
    - Streeter, David, 1971-1973 (Box 24:, Folder 383)
    - Sturgeon, Tandy, 1977-1988 (Box 24:, Folder 384)
    - Tansy Press (see: Moritz, John)
    - Universita degli Studi di Ferenze (see: Binni, Francesco)
    - University College (see: Montgomery, Stuart)
    - University of California Press (see: Wesling, Donald)
    - University of California, Los Angeles (see: Golding, Alan)
    - University of California, San Diego (see: Davidson, Michael, Wesling, Donald)
    - University of Colorado, Boulder (see: Levitt, Paul, Williams, Raymond)
    - University of Connecticut (see: Butterick, George)
    - University of Durham (see: Caddel, Ric)
    - University of Edinburgh (see: Lopez, Tony)
    - University of Essex (see: Butterfield, Herb, Brotherston, Gordon, Davie, Donald)
    - University of Louisville (see: Golding, Alan)
    - University of Mississippi (see: Golding, Alan)
    - University of New Mexico (see: Bartlett, Lee)
    - University of New Orleans (see: Dailey, Joel, Gery, John)
    - University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg (see: Blevins, Rich)
    - University of Southwestern Louisiana (see: Fox, Willard, Fackler, Herb)
    - University of Toledo (see: Lipman, Joel)
    - University of Wisconsin (see: Sturgeon, Tandy)
    - University of Wisconsin-Parkside (see: Streeter, David)
    - Vas Dias, Robert, 1975-1976 (Box 24:, Folder 385)
    - Vassar College (see: Peck, Daniel)
    - Waldeman, Anne, 1972-1985 (Box 24:, Folder 386)
    - Warner, Patrick, 1986-1988 (Box 24:, Folder 387)
    - Warren, Kenneth, 1985-1987 (Box 24:, Folder 388)
    - Watson, William “Rich”, 1975 (Box 24:, Folder 389)
    - Webster, Lee, 1982 (Box 24:, Folder 390)
    - Wesling, Donald, 1971-1990 (Box 24:, Folder 391)
    - Wiater, Michael, 1972-1974 (Box 24:, Folder 392)
    - Wieners, John, 1957-1973 (Box 25:, Folder 393)
    - Wilkinson, John, 1974 (Box 25:, Folder 394)
    - William Morrow & Company (see: Johnson, Joyce)
    - Williams, Raymond, 1988-1991 (Box 25:, Folder 395)
    - Wind Vein Press (see: Preston, Scott)
    - Wingbow Press, 1979-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 396)
    - Wolff, John, 1983-1990 (Box 25:, Folder 397)
    - Woolf, Doug, 1963-1987 (Box 25:, Folder 398)
    - Wray, Ron, 1977-1984 (Box 25:, Folder 399)
    - Young, David, 1976-1987 (Box 25:, Folder 400)
  - Subseries B: Minor Correspondence, 1962-1993
    - Unidentified Correspondents, undated (Box 26:, Folder 401)
    - Unidentified Correspondents, undated (Box 26:, Folder 402)
    - Unidentified Correspondents, undated (Box 26:, Folder 403)
    - Undated A (Box 26:, Folder 404)
    - Undated B (Box 26:, Folder 405)
    - Undated C (Box 26:, Folder 406)
    - Undated D (Box 26:, Folder 407)
    - Undated E (Box 27:, Folder 408)
    - Undated F (Box 27:, Folder 409)
    - Undated G (Box 27:, Folder 410)
    - Undated H (Box 27:, Folder 411)
    - Undated I - J (Box 27:, Folder 412)
    - Undated K (Box 27:, Folder 413)
    - Undated L (Box 27:, Folder 414)
    - Undated M (Box 27:, Folder 415)
    - Undated N - O (Box 27:, Folder 416)
    - Undated P (Box 27:, Folder 417)
    - Undated Q - R (Box 27:, Folder 418)
    - Undated S (Box 27:, Folder 419)
    - Undated T - U (Box 27:, Folder 420)
    - Undated W - Z (Box 27:, Folder 421)
    - A - Z, 1962 (Box 30:, Folder 464)
    - A - Z, 1964 (Box 30:, Folder 465)
    - A - Z, 1965 (Box 30:, Folder 466)
    - Unidentified Author, 1965 (Box 30:, Folder 467)
    - A - Z, 1966 (Box 30:, Folder 468)
    - A - Z, 1967 (Box 30:, Folder 469)
    - A - Z, 1968 (Box 30:, Folder 470)
    - A - Z, 1969 (Box 30:, Folder 471)
    - A - Z, 1970 (Box 30:, Folder 472)
    - A - Z, 1971 (Box 30:, Folder 473)
    - Unidentified Author, 1971 (Box 30:, Folder 474)
    - A - R, 1972 (Box 30:, Folder 475)
    - S - Z, 1972 (Box 30:, Folder 476)
    - Unidentified Author, 1972 (Box 30:, Folder 477)